(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Sheldon:)-Embarrassed you?
-You know what?
(Amy:)I don't have time for this.
Find another way home.
(Sheldon:)I'm starting to get the sense
that you're angry with me.
(Amy:)-Really? What tipped you off?
-Couple things, actually.
(Sheldon:)Your tone of voice,
your body language--
(Amy:)-Get out.
-Well, now, that.
Image number six: woman giving birth.
Oh!
It's 9:00. Where you been?
(Sheldon:)I had to take the bus home.
(Sheldon:)Fell asleep and missed my stop.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
(Sheldon:)Did you know that Los Angeles has
a Little Sri Lanka?
(Leonard:)-I did not.
-Well, I do... now.
(Sheldon:)They're a lovely people.
(Sheldon:)Although terrifying when you wake up
face-to-face with them.
(Sheldon:)If you're hungry, I brought home
some mutton in coconut milk.